Guide to the Buck Downs literary papers, 1984-2009 MS2270
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Buck Downs literary papers
1984-2009
1988-2006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Downs, Buck
MS2270
14 Linear Feet
This collection contains correspondence, postcards, handwritten/typed manuscripts, photographs, pre-publication proofs, art, and flyers. This material dates from 1984-2009 with the majority of the material falling within the dates 1988-2006. Most of the material consists of items mailed or sent to Buck Downs from other artists, poets, publisher, authors, and friends. Most of the material (whether typed manuscripts or graphic art) includes original poetry. This collection also contains some Buck Downs poems and professional papers.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement note
This Collection is organized into two series: Correspondence to Buck Downs and Poems and other paper.
Scope and Content note
This collection contains correspondence, poems, postcards, handwritten/typed manuscripts, photographs, pre-publication proofs, slides, VHS/audio tapes, folk art (including paintings, papier-mâché, photographs, and collages), flyers, and article clippings. This material dates from 1984-2009 with the majority of the material falling within the dates 1988-2006. This collection consists of material gathered and/or created by Buck Downs. Most of the material consists of items mailed or sent to Buck Downs from other artists, poets, publisher, authors, and friends. Most of the material (whether typed manuscripts or graphic art) includes original poetry. Some of the material was sent to Buck Downs in consideration for publication. There is a large amount of material from Brett Evans. There are fair to substantial amounts of material from Jules Boykoff, Jeff Conant, CA Conrad, Jessica Freeman, Greg Fuchs, Heather Fuller, John McNally, Joe Ross, Rod Smith, and Ficus Strangulensis. This collection also contains Buck Down poems and professional papers (mostly in series two). The collection was donated by Buck Downs in 2009.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Buck Downs, 05/01/2009, [2009.031]
Biographical/Historical note
Buck Downs (1964-) is a poet, publisher, and editor who has been a long-time resident of Washington, D.C. Bucks Jordan Downs was born in Jones County, Mississippi on 07/28/1964. His parents are Jordon Downs and Fronia Gail Ulmer Downs. Buck Downs resides and works in Washington, D.C. Some of his poems have appeared in journals including Puppyflowers, Brooklyn Rail, and Columbia Poetry Review. His books include Ladies Love Outlaws, In Memory of D. Thompson, Small Pieces Loosely Joined, twist riffs & stiff hits, Recreational Vehicle, and Marijuana Softdrink. He is renowned for his high energy reading style. His CD Pontiac Fever was released by Narrow House Recordings in 2006. Buck is editor of Open 24 Hours and was formerly editor of other publications.
Part of this collection reflects his postcard project: "The postcard project began to find its current shape in 1993. I had been hand-typing individual poem-postcards, mailing them to poetry/art friends like Brett Evans, while concurrently doing the small-poet thing of compiling, mailing, and tracking responses to manuscripts from mostly presses and zines. The latter enterprise was depressing and unproductive, even when successful, while the poem-postcards turned out to be a positive hoot. So in the summer of 1993 I gave up the habit of sending work to magazine editors, and raided my address book to build a list of people whose opinions mattered to me. Since sometime in late 1993, I have kept a mailing list and sent out a monthly poem on a post card. The list has grown from a handful of friends to a couple hundred people" (Buck Downs, Dec. 2007).
Experimental poetry -- 20th century.; Poets, American
- Correspondence to Buck Downs, 1984-2009; 1988-2006; Series 1; 13.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Content note
  This series contains correspondence, poems, postcards, handwritten/typed manuscripts, photographs, pre-publication proofs, slides, VHS/audio tapes, folk art (including paintings, papier-mâché, photographs, and collages), flyers, and article clippings. This material dates from 1984-2009 with the majority of the material falling within the dates 1988-2006. This collection consists of material gathered by Buck Downs. Most of the material consists of items mailed or sent to Buck Downs from other artists, poets, publisher, authors, and friends. Most of the material (whether typed manuscripts or graphic art) includes original poetry. Some of the material was sent to Buck Downs in consideration for publication. There is a large amount of material from Brett Evans. There are fair to substantial amounts of material from Jules Boykoff, Jeff Conant, CA Conrad, Jessica Freeman, Greg Fuchs, Heather Fuller, John McNally, Joe Ross, Rod Smith, and Ficus Strangulensis.
  Arrangement note
  The Correspondence to Buck Downs series is arranged alphabetically by last names, which is how the collection was organized when donated. Folders are labeled by full name. Some individuals have multiple folders containing their correspondence. Materials are not arranged within folders. There are also miscellaneous files labeled by first letter of last names (ex. Misc. H or Misc. P) for cases where there were few items from an individual.
  - Albo, Mike, 03/24/1992 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Amorello, Robert, 09/06/1994-03/30/1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Andrews, Bruce, 1993-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arrizza, John, 10/10/1992 and 3/11/1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ashton, Ken, 1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bagato, Jeff, 03/01/1995; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Baratier, David, 07/19/2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Basinski, Michael, 05/02/1995-12/2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Berrigan, Anselm, 02/1997 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Boykoff, Jules [1 of 3], 2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Boykoff, Jules [2 of 3], 2003-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Boykoff, Jules [3 of 3], 2004-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Misc. B, 1994-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Camero, Jimi, 2005-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Campbell, Ken, 1991-1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cardarelli, Joseph, 07/01/1994 and 10/25/1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Chirot, David, 06/29/2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Coletti, John, undates, circa 2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Colley, Don, 1984-2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Conant, Jeff [1 of 3], 1994-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Conant, Jeff [2 of 3], 1991-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Conant, Jeff [3 of 3], 1993-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Conner, Kyle, 09/22/2000-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Conrad, CA [1 of 3], 1998-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Conrad, CA [2 of 3], 2000-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Conrad, CA [3 of 3], 2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Crews, Judson, 1985-1991; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Misc. C, 1993-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dailey, Joel, 1996-2003; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dalachinsky, Steve [1 of 2], 2001-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dalachinsky, Steve [2 of 2], 2002-2009; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Danko, Stephen III, circa 2003 - 2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Darragh, Tina, 1995-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Davies, Alan, 1999-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Tim (New Direction Publishing), 1997-1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Tim (New Direction Publishing), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Deming, Richard / Nancy Kuhl / Phylum Press, 2003-2009; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Dominici, Michael [1 of 2], circa 1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dominici, Michael [2 of 2], 1993-1995 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - DuPlessis, Rachel, 2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Dunlap, William, 1989-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Evans, Brett, 1989-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Brett, 1989-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Brett, 1996-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Brett, 1994-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Evans, Brett, 1994-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Brett, 1991-1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Brett, 1991-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Brett, 1990-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Evans, Brett, 1990-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Brett, 1997-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Brett, 2003-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Brett, undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Evans, Brett, 1991-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Evans, Brett, 2004-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Brett, 1989-1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Brett, 1991-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Brett, 1992-1997; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Evans, Brett, 1988-1995; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Brett, 1994-2003; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Evans, Brett, 1992-1997; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Evans, Brett, 1991-1997; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Brett, 1990-1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Eisenhower, Cathy, 2004-2005 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ewing, Blair, 2002-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Fast, 2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fitterman, Rob, 1990-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Fitterman, Rob and Buck Down Books, 1993-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Fitterman, Rob and Buck Down Books, 1988-1995; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Foust, Grahm, circa 1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Francis, Ke, 1992-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Franks, David, 1993-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Frederick, Helen [1 of 2], 1991-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Frederick, Helen [2 of 2], 1992-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Freeman, Jessica [1 of 3], circa 1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Freeman, Jessica [2 of 3], 1987-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Freeman, Jessica [3 of 3], 1991-1997; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Friedlander, Benjamin, 1995-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Fuchs, Greg [1 of 6], 2003 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Fuchs, Greg [2 of 6], 1989-2003; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Fuchs, Greg [3 of 6], 1992-1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Fuchs, Greg [4 of 6], 1996-1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Fuchs, Greg [5 of 6], circa 1991 - circa 1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fuchs, Greg [6 of 6], 1992-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fuller, Heather [1 of 4], 1996-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fuller, Heather [2 of 4], 1998-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Fuller, Heather [3 of 4], 1997-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Fuller, Heather [4 of 4], 1998-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Misc. F, circa 1993 - circa 1995; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Gardner, Drew, 1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Gardner, Jeremy, 2004-2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Gaspar, Greig, 2007-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Goodchild, Trevor, 2002-2003; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Goodwin, Chirs, 2001-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Misc. G, 1994-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Haymon, Ava Learell [1 of 2], 1988-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Haymon, Ava Learell [2 of 2], 1991-1992 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Head, Robert, 1994-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Hibbard, Tom [1 of 2], 1993-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hibbard, Tom [2 of 2], 1992-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hollo, Anselm, 1988-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hompson, Davi Det, 1994-1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Honeycott, Brece, 1996-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Howe, William R., circa 1996 - circa 1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hughes, Esther [1 of 2], 1987-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Hughes, Esther [2 of 2], 1996-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hunter, Liese, 1987-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Misc. H, 1997-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Iijima, Brenda, 2004-2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ioanes, Ellen, 2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, Nicholas [1 of 2], 2004-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Nicholas [2 of 2], 2006-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Joselow, Beth, 03/07/2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Keckler, WB, 1995-1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Killian, Kevin, 1999-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - King, Sigrid, 1988-1989; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - King, Susan, 1991 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Misc. K, 2001-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Landers, Susan, 1997-1999; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Lang, Doug, undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Larkin, Maryrose, 1997 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lazer, Hank, 1994-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Levi, Alan, 1992-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Levy, Andrew, 1994-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Massey, Joseph, 2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - McCreary, Chris and Jenn, circa 2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - McNally, John [1 of 4], 1988-1993; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - McNally, John [2 of 4], 1989-1993; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - McNally, John [3 of 4], undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - McNally, John [4 of 4], 1989-1993; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Mirakove, Carol, 2001-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Mitts, Tom, 1991-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Mullin, Larry, 1993-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Murphy, Shelia, 1992-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Myles, Eileen, 1991-1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Misc. M, 1993-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Nash, Susan Smith, 1991-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Nguyen, Hoa, 1995-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Nelms, Sheryl, 2003-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Nielsen, Aldon, 1992-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Notley, Alice, 1991-1993; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Misc. N, 1993-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Misc. O, circa 1995 - circa 1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Parrish, Tim, 1990-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Pestal, Michael, 1989-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Putman, C.E. [1 of 2], undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Putman, C.E. [2 of 2], 1999-2001; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Misc. P, 2000-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Raworth, Tom, 2005-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Rebaza-Soruluz, Luis, 1991 and undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Rosenthal, Laura, 1988-1995; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Rosenzweig, Phyllis, 1996-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ross, Joe [1 of 3], undated; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Ross, Joe [2 of 3], 1986-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Ross, Joe [3 of 3], 1993-1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Misc. R, 2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, Cecil, 1990-1991; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Selby, Spencer, 1988-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Sherlock, Frank, 1997; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Rod [1 of 3], circa 1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Rod [2 of 3], circa 1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Rod [3 of 3], 1993-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Sokolowski, Michael, 2007-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Sonnennfeld, Mark, 2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Strangulensis, Ficus [1 of 4], 2001-2004; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Strangulensis, Ficus [2 of 4], 2004-2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Strangulensis, Ficus [3 of 4], 2005-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Strangulensis, Ficus [4 of 4], 2005-2009; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Stroffolino, Chris, circa 1991; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Misc. S, 1991-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Tassin, Sonia Denise, 2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Taylor, Harry, 1991-1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Taylor, Ross, 1997; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Thomas Lowe, 1995-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Thompson, Eric, 1991-1998; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Thorson, Maureen, 2006-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Thurston, Kevin, circa 2005; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Toll, Chris, 1988-2006; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Misc. T, 1994-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Van Horn, Erica / Simon Cutts / Coracle Press, 2006-2009; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Verlinden, John, circa 1989; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Vitiello, Chris, 1994-2000; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Wallace, Mark [1 of 2], 1993-1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Wallace, Mark [2 of 2], circa 1996; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Washington Review, 2001-2002; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - West, Wendy, 1993-1994; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Wondra, Janet, 1992; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Wright, Terry, 1993; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Young, Geoff, 1990-2008; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Misc. W, V, and Y, 1997-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Misc. / unknown, 1987-2007; MS2270 Series 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Poems and other papers, 1986-1994; Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series currently consists of one box of material with six folders: two folders of poetry, two folders of professional material, and two folders containing a mix of poems, flyers, and other papers.
  This series contains poems, notes, handwritten/typed manuscripts, pre-publication proofs, flyers, professional material, and other papers. This material dates from 1986-1994. This series consists of material gathered and/or created by Buck Downs, particularly some of his poems and professional papers.
  - Poems 1986-1988 by Buck Downs, MS2270 Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Poems, circa 1989 - circa 1990; MS2270 Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Visual Artists Public Projects, Pyramid Atlantic, 1990-1994; MS2270 Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Poems, flyers, misc. papers [1 of 2], 1989-1994; MS2270 Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Poems, flyers, misc. papers [2 of 2], circa 1986 - circa 1989; MS2270 Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Score for local knowlegde draft materials, 2006; MS2270 Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 6)